<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="compcache">压缩页面并保持在内存中以提高它的容量。这可以使用更多的程序可以在内存中运行，但是占用更多的 CPU 时间。它也同时激活 SWAP。</string>
	<string name="compcachedisk">压缩缓存的大小</string>
	<string name="swap">Android 使用交换空间做为额外的内存使用，可以使应用程序在不激活时保留在交换空间上。交换空间增加了系统的虚拟内存数量。如果没有建立 SWAP 分区，可以先使用复模式建立。你需要有外置 SD 卡（推荐使用 Class 6 的高速卡）。</string>
	<string name="overclock1">超频你的处理器到 614 MHz。</string>
	<string name="overclock2">超频你的处理器到 710 MHz。有些手机会不稳定。</string>
	<string name="sampling">这是手机获取它的负载的时间间隔。每次采样后，手机会增加或减少 CPU 速度来调整负载。</string>
	<string name="sensors">所有传感器的反应速度。</string>
	<string name="ssh">允许你从电脑上运行一个在你的 Galaxy 上的 Linux 终端。</string>
	<string name="renice">改变正在运行程序的优先优先级。</string>
	<string name="provisionned">你可以无 SIM 卡时使用你的 Galaxy。</string>
	<string name="vnc">你可以从电脑上控制你的手机（使用指定的程序）。</string>
	<string name="bootani">使用小的开机动画以减少启动时间。</string>
	<string name="servicemode">只有专家可以使用！你可以调整声音设置等。</string>
	<string name="kitchen">建立你自己的 Google 应用程序包。</string>
	<string name="memorythresholds">These are the thresholds from which the device will kill some processes, to free memory (below these thresholds, internal task killer will kill these apps). Make a Nandroid Backup before!</string>
	<string name="foregroundapp">This is the application currently on the screen, and running. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="visibleapp">This is an application that is open, and running in the background because it is still doing something. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="secondaryapp">This is a process (a service that an application needs) that is alive and ready in case it is needed to do something. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="hiddenapp">This again is a process, that sits idle (but still alive) in case it is needed by an app that is alive and running. Be careful with this setting!</string>
	<string name="contentapp">They are applications that provide data (content) to the system. So are things like the Android Market, or Google Sync. If they are alive, they can refresh and provide the content they are supposed to at the set interval. If you kill them, they can not of course.</string>
	<string name="emptyapp">We call these "ghosts." They are applications that you have opened, but are done with them. Android uses a unique style of handling memory management. When an activity is ended, instead of killing it off Android keeps the application in memory so that opening them again is a faster process. Theses "ghost" applications use no battery or CPU time, they just fill RAM that would be otherwise empty. When this memory is needed by a different application or process, the RAM is flushed and made available for the new application.</string>	
</resources>