<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="compcache">Comprimeren van RAM maakt het RAM virtueel groter. Dit geeft extra ruimte voor applicaties, maar kost ook meer rekentijd. Hiermee wordt ook swap geactiveerd.</string>
	<string name="compcachedisk">De grootte van het Compcache.</string>
	<string name="swap">Android gebruikt swap als "extra" geheugen voor applicaties die niet actief worden gebruikt, maar wel zijn gewijzigd. De swap ruimte en de hoeveel RAM samen maken het virtuele RAM geheugen van het systeem. Maak eerst een swap partitie aan met behulp van recovery. Hier is een externe SD kaart voor nodig. (Class 6 wordt aangeraden)</string>
	<string name="overclock1">Geeft meer rekensnelheid, ten koste van batterijduur.</string>
	<string name="overclock2">Op sommige devices niet stabiel. Geeft meer rekensnelheid, ten koste van batterijduur.</string>
	<string name="sampling">Is bepalend voor de reactiesnelheid van het schalen van de CPU. Lager is sneller.</string>
	<string name="sensors">Is bepalend voor de reactiesnelheid van de sensoren. Lager is sneller.</string>
	<string name="ssh">Gebruik SSH om in te loggen op je Galaxy.</string>
	<string name="renice">Renice past de prioriteit van een of meerdere processes aan.</string>
	<string name="provisionned">Laat je je Galaxy gebruiken zonder SIM.</string>
	<string name="vnc">Gebruik VNC om je Galaxy te besturen.</string>
	<string name="bootani">Een kleinere opstartanimatie resulteert in een kortere opstarttijd.</string>
	<string name="servicemode">Alleen voor experts! Hier kun je de audiohack activeren.</string>
	<string name="kitchen">Maak hier je eigen pakket met Google Apps.</string>
	<string name="memorythresholds">These are the thresholds from which the device will kill some processes, to free memory (below these thresholds, internal task killer will kill these apps). Make a Nandroid Backup before!</string>
	<string name="foregroundapp">This is the application currently on the screen, and running. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="visibleapp">This is an application that is open, and running in the background because it is still doing something. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="secondaryapp">This is a process (a service that an application needs) that is alive and ready in case it is needed to do something. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="hiddenapp">This again is a process, that sits idle (but still alive) in case it is needed by an app that is alive and running. Be careful with this setting!</string>
	<string name="contentapp">They are applications that provide data (content) to the system. So are things like the Android Market, or Google Sync. If they are alive, they can refresh and provide the content they are supposed to at the set interval. If you kill them, they can not of course.</string>
	<string name="emptyapp">We call these "ghosts." They are applications that you have opened, but are done with them. Android uses a unique style of handling memory management. When an activity is ended, instead of killing it off Android keeps the application in memory so that opening them again is a faster process. Theses "ghost" applications use no battery or CPU time, they just fill RAM that would be otherwise empty. When this memory is needed by a different application or process, the RAM is flushed and made available for the new application.</string>	
</resources>