<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="compcache">Compressione pagine nella memoria RAM virtuale aumentandone la disponibilità. Consente la gestione di più applicazioni a parità di memoria disponibile. Richiede lavoro aggiuntivo per la CPU. Richiede l´attivazione della memoria SWAP.</string>
    <string name="compcachedisk">Dimensione di compcache</string>
    <string name="swap">Android utilizza la memoria SWAP per aumentare la memoria a disposizione; utile per applicazioni che lavorano in background, utilizzate meno frequentemente o che richiedono molta memoria. La memoria SWAP aumenta la memoria virtuale a disposizione. Prima di attivare creare la partizione SWAP mediante l´opzione in recovery. Necessaria MicroSD esterna (consigliata Classe6).</string>
    <string name="overclock1">Overclocca il processore a 614 MHz. MHz.</string>
    <string name="overclock2">Overclocca il processore a 710 MHz. Instabile su alcuni telefoni.</string>
    <string name="sampling">Intervallo di tempo in cui il processore analizza il carico di lavoro. Dopo l´analisi, viene aumentata o diminuita la frequenza della CPU in base al carico.</string>
  	<string name="sensors">Velocità di reazione dei sensori.</string>
    <string name="ssh">Possibilità di aprire un terminale Linux dal PC sul Galaxy.</string>
    <string name="renice">Renice modifica le priorità di esecuzione dei processi attivi.</string>
  	<string name="provisionned">Possibilità di utilizzo del Galaxy senza SIM Card.</string>
    <string name="vnc">Possibilità di controllare il Galaxy dal proprio computer attraverso un´applicazione specifica.</string>
    <string name="bootani">Utilizza una  bootanimation più leggera per velocizzare l´avvio del telefono.</string>
    <string name="servicemode">Per esperti! Possibilità di applicare Hack dell´Audio.</string>
    <string name="kitchen">Crea un pacchetto personalizzato di applicazioni Google.</string>
	<string name="memorythresholds">These are the thresholds from which the device will kill some processes, to free memory (below these thresholds, internal task killer will kill these apps). Make a Nandroid Backup before!</string>
	<string name="foregroundapp">This is the application currently on the screen, and running. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="visibleapp">This is an application that is open, and running in the background because it is still doing something. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="secondaryapp">This is a process (a service that an application needs) that is alive and ready in case it is needed to do something. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="hiddenapp">This again is a process, that sits idle (but still alive) in case it is needed by an app that is alive and running. Be careful with this setting!</string>
	<string name="contentapp">They are applications that provide data (content) to the system. So are things like the Android Market, or Google Sync. If they are alive, they can refresh and provide the content they are supposed to at the set interval. If you kill them, they can not of course.</string>
	<string name="emptyapp">We call these "ghosts." They are applications that you have opened, but are done with them. Android uses a unique style of handling memory management. When an activity is ended, instead of killing it off Android keeps the application in memory so that opening them again is a faster process. Theses "ghost" applications use no battery or CPU time, they just fill RAM that would be otherwise empty. When this memory is needed by a different application or process, the RAM is flushed and made available for the new application.</string>	
</resources>