<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="swap">Android uses swap space as "extra" memory. You need a external SD Card.</string>
	<string name="sampling">Threshold check interval. Only ondemand gov.</string>
	<string name="ssh">Allows you to run a Linux shell from your PC on your Galaxy.</string>
	<string name="provisionned">You can use your Galaxy without a SIM Card.</string>
	<string name="vnc">You can control your phone from your computer.</string>
	<string name="bootani">Use a smaller bootanimation to decrease boot time.</string>
	<string name="servicemode">For experts only! You can apply Audio Hack here.</string>
	<string name="memorythresholds">These are the thresholds from which the device will kill some processes, to free memory.</string>
	<string name="foregroundapp">This is the application currently on the screen, and running.</string>
	<string name="visibleapp">This is an application that is open, and running in the background because it is still doing something.</string>
	<string name="secondaryapp">This is a process (a service that an application needs) that is alive and ready in case it is needed to do something.</string>
	<string name="hiddenapp">This again is a process, that sits idle (but still alive) in case it is needed by an app that is alive and running.</string>
	<string name="contentapp">They are applications that provide data (content) to the system. So are things like the Android Market, or Google Sync.</string>
	<string name="emptyapp">We call these "ghosts." They are applications that you have opened, but are done with them.</string>
	<string name="lcddensity">Lowering the density value will "expand" the screen, allowing to see more without scrolling. Make a Nandroid Backup before!</string>
	<string name="compcalibration">This will reset some compass settings.</string>
	<string name="presets">Select you preferred setting</string>
	<string name="swappiness">How much Android should use Swap.</string>
	<string name="sdcache">Higher values will boost SD reading speed.</string>
	<string name="gmail">In Germany you can not download GMail app. Press apply to bypass this restriction. Search for "Google Mail".</string>
	<string name="clearcache">Tells kernel to drop caches and your device will be snappy again. There is a GAOSP Conf widget which will do this for you automatically.</string>
	<string name="wifi">Time between Wifi scan intervals.</string>
	<string name="updateinterval">This widget will clear cache every 3 hours. Useful if you use swap because it clears everything and speeds up your Galaxy. You can also click on the widget to do this manually.</string>
	<string name="systemapps">This can slightly speed up your phone.</string>
	<string name="fotakill">Prevents OTA updates (Samsung will not release OTA updates for Galaxy).</string>
	<string name="threshold">When the CPU load reaches this point, the governor will scale the CPU up. Only ondemand gov.</string>
	<string name="bias">Setting this value higher will "bias" the governor toward lower frequencies. Only ondemand gov.</string>
	<string name="niceload">System will ignore higher background process priorities (saves battery) Only ondemand gov.</string>
	<string name="fudgeswap">Use a specified amount of Swap and Compcache as free memory. High values can cause slowdowns.</string>
</resources>