<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="swap">Android uses swap space as "extra" memory for pages of application memory that are not being actively used by the application but have been modified (written to). The swap space size plus RAM size is the total amount of virtual memory for the system. Create swap partition with recovery mode first. You need a external SD card (Class 6 recommend). Compcache will be disabled.</string>
	<string name="overclock1">Overclocking your processor to 614 MHz.</string>
	<string name="overclock2">Overclocking your processor to 710 MHz. Unstable on some devices.</string>
	<string name="sampling">It is the time interval in which the device gets its own load. After each sample, device increases or decreases cpu speed regarding the load.</string>
	<string name="sensors">How fast all Sensors will react.</string>
	<string name="ssh">Allows you to run a Linux shell from your PC on your Galaxy.</string>
	<string name="renice">Renice alters the scheduling priority of one or more running processes.</string>
	<string name="provisionned">You can use your Galaxy without a SIM Card.</string>
	<string name="vnc">You can control your phone from your computer (using a specialized app).</string>
	<string name="bootani">Uses a smaller bootanimation to decrease boot time.</string>
	<string name="servicemode">For experts only! You can apply Audio Hack here.</string>
	<string name="kitchen">Create your own custom Google Application Package.</string>
	<string name="memorythresholds">These are the thresholds from which the device will kill some processes, to free memory (below these thresholds, internal task killer will kill these apps). Make a Nandroid Backup before!</string>
	<string name="foregroundapp">This is the application currently on the screen, and running. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="visibleapp">This is an application that is open, and running in the background because it is still doing something. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="secondaryapp">This is a process (a service that an application needs) that is alive and ready in case it is needed to do something. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="hiddenapp">This again is a process, that sits idle (but still alive) in case it is needed by an app that is alive and running. Be careful with this setting!</string>
	<string name="contentapp">They are applications that provide data (content) to the system. So are things like the Android Market, or Google Sync. If they are alive, they can refresh and provide the content they are supposed to at the set interval. If you kill them, they can not of course.</string>
	<string name="emptyapp">We call these "ghosts." They are applications that you have opened, but are done with them. Android uses a unique style of handling memory management. When an activity is ended, instead of killing it off Android keeps the application in memory so that opening them again is a faster process. Theses "ghost" applications use no battery or CPU time, they just fill RAM that would be otherwise empty. When this memory is needed by a different application or process, the RAM is flushed and made available for the new application.</string>
	<string name="lcddensity">Lowering the density value will then expand the screen, allowing text to appear longer and not have to scroll or wrap as soon. It also increases spacing between home screen icons, which might come in handy if someone uses Multicon Widget or ADW Launcher’s columns change to pack in more shortcuts. Make a Nandroid Backup before!</string>
</resources>