<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="swap">Android uses swap space as "extra" memory. You need a external SD Card.</string>
	<string name="sampling">Threshold check intervall. Only ondemand governor.</string>
	<string name="ssh">Allows you to run a Linux shell from your PC on your Galaxy.</string>
	<string name="renice">Renice alters the scheduling priority of one or more running processes.</string>
	<string name="provisionned">You can use your Galaxy without a SIM Card.</string>
	<string name="vnc">You can control your phone from your computer.</string>
	<string name="bootani">Use a smaller bootanimation to decrease boot time.</string>
	<string name="servicemode">For experts only! You can apply Audio Hack here.</string>
	<string name="memorythresholds">These are the thresholds from which the device will kill some processes, to free memory.</string>
	<string name="foregroundapp">This is the application currently on the screen, and running. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="visibleapp">This is an application that is open, and running in the background because it is still doing something. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="secondaryapp">This is a process (a service that an application needs) that is alive and ready in case it is needed to do something. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="hiddenapp">This again is a process, that sits idle (but still alive) in case it is needed by an app that is alive and running. Be careful with this setting!</string>
	<string name="contentapp">They are applications that provide data (content) to the system. So are things like the Android Market, or Google Sync. If they are alive, they can refresh and provide the content they are supposed to at the set interval. If you kill them, they can not of course.</string>
	<string name="emptyapp">We call these "ghosts." They are applications that you have opened, but are done with them. Android uses a unique style of handling memory management. When an activity is ended, instead of killing it off Android keeps the application in memory so that opening them again is a faster process. Theses "ghost" applications use no battery or CPU time, they just fill RAM that would be otherwise empty. When this memory is needed by a different application or process, the RAM is flushed and made available for the new application.</string>
	<string name="lcddensity">Lowering the density value will "expand" the screen, allowing to see more without scrolling. Make a Nandroid Backup before!</string>
	<string name="compcalibration">This will reset some compass settings.</string>
	<string name="presets">Select you preferred setting</string>
	<string name="swappiness">How much Android should use Swap (%)</string>
	<string name="sdcache">Higher values will boost SD reading speed.</string>
	<string name="gmail">In Germany you can not download GMail app. Press apply to bypass this restriction. Search for "Google Mail".</string>
	<string name="clearcache">Tells kernel to drop caches and your device will be snappy again. Should be applied once a day if you do not reboot your device.</string>
	<string name="wifi">Time between Wifi scan intervals (s)</string>
</resources>