<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="compcache">Sıkıştırılmış sayfaları RAM´de tutmak kapasiteyi arttırır. Bu, varolan alanda daha fazla program çalıştırılmasını sağlar. Ama daha fazla CPU süresi gerektirir. Aynı zamanda Swap´ı etkinleştirir.</string>
	<string name="compcachedisk">Compcache büyüklüğü</string>
	<string name="swap">Android,aktif ama uygulama belleği tarafından kullanılmayan,uygulama belleği sayfaları için "ekstra" bellek olarak takas alanı kullanır. Takas alanı ve RAM´in toplam büyüklüğü sistemin sanal bellek alanıdır. Öncelikle recovery modda takas bölümü oluşturun. Harici bir SD karta ihtiyacınız var.(Önerilen kart tipi Class 6).</string>
	<string name="overclock1">İşlemciniz 614 Mhz´e overclock ediliyor.</string>
	<string name="overclock2">İşlemciniz 710 Mhz´e overclock ediliyor. Bazı cihazlarda kararsızlığa neden olabilir.</string>
	<string name="sampling">Her örneklemeden sonra işlemci hızı yüke bağlı olarak artar veya azalır.</string>
	<string name="sensors">Sensörlerin ne kadar hızlı tepki vereceği.</string>
	<string name="ssh">PC2niz üzerinden Galaxy´de Linux shellerini çalıştırmanıza izin verir.</string>
	<string name="renice">Renice, çalışmakta olan bir veya daha fazla programın öncelik sırasını belirler.</string>
	<string name="provisionned">Galaxy´nizi SIM Kart olmadan kullanabilirsiniz.</string>
	<string name="vnc">Telefonunuzu bilgisayardan kontrol edebilirsiniz.(özel programlar kullanarak).</string>
	<string name="bootani">Açılış süresini kısaltmak için daha hafif bir açılış animasyonu kullanır.</string>
	<string name="servicemode">Sadece profesyoneller için! Audio Hack´i burdan yapabilirsiniz.</string>
	<string name="kitchen">Kendi Google Program Paketinizi oluşturun.</string>
	<string name="memorythresholds">These are the thresholds from which the device will kill some processes, to free memory (below these thresholds, internal task killer will kill these apps). Make a Nandroid Backup before!</string>
	<string name="foregroundapp">This is the application currently on the screen, and running. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="visibleapp">This is an application that is open, and running in the background because it is still doing something. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="secondaryapp">This is a process (a service that an application needs) that is alive and ready in case it is needed to do something. Do not change this value unless you have much knowledge about that!</string>
	<string name="hiddenapp">This again is a process, that sits idle (but still alive) in case it is needed by an app that is alive and running. Be careful with this setting!</string>
	<string name="contentapp">They are applications that provide data (content) to the system. So are things like the Android Market, or Google Sync. If they are alive, they can refresh and provide the content they are supposed to at the set interval. If you kill them, they can not of course.</string>
	<string name="emptyapp">We call these "ghosts." They are applications that you have opened, but are done with them. Android uses a unique style of handling memory management. When an activity is ended, instead of killing it off Android keeps the application in memory so that opening them again is a faster process. Theses "ghost" applications use no battery or CPU time, they just fill RAM that would be otherwise empty. When this memory is needed by a different application or process, the RAM is flushed and made available for the new application.</string>	
</resources>